const quizeDataStructure = [
  {
    "eventID": "1 ",
    "Question": " What is the main color of Brazil’s national team shirt?",
    "Options": [
      "Red ",
      "Black ",
      "Pink ",
      "Yellow "
    ],
    "ans": "Yellow ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": "Where were the 2002 Football world cup finals held? ",
    "Options": [
      "Japan & Korea ",
      " Germany",
      "Scotland ",
      "Colombo "
    ],
    "ans": "Japan & Korea ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": " A spot-kick is taken from where?",
    "Options": [
      "The Center Spot ",
      "The Penalty Spot ",
      "The Ink Spot ",
      "On The Spot "
    ],
    "ans": "The Penalty Spot ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Easy"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": " The penalty area is usually how far from the touch line?",
    "Options": [
      " 18 yards",
      " 15 yards",
      "22 yards ",
      " 4 yards"
    ],
    "ans": "18 yards ",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "5 ",
    "Question": "When was the inaugural Premier League season? ",
    "Options": [
      " 1992-93",
      "1995-73 ",
      "1990-92 ",
      "2002-04 "
    ],
    "ans": " 1992-93",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": " Easy"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "6 ",
    "Question": "Which country has won the most world cups? ",
    "Options": [
      "Uruguay ",
      " Germany",
      " Agtentina",
      " Brazil"
    ],
    "ans": "Brazil ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Easy"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "7 ",
    "Question": " Who is the Champions League’s top goalscorer of all time?",
    "Options": [
      "Ryan Giggs ",
      " Lionel Messy",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo ",
      " Neymar"
    ],
    "ans": "Cristiano Ronaldo ",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": " Easy"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 8",
    "Question": "Who holds the record for top Bundesliga goalscorers of all time? ",
    "Options": [
      "Gerd Muller ",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo ",
      "Neymar ",
      "Samuel Eto’o "
    ],
    "ans": " ",
    "eventCtg": " ",
    "quizCtg": " Easy"
  }
]



                                                                   Footbal  / Normal

const quizeDtatStructure = [
  {
    "eventID": " 1",
    "Question": " Which of the following country hosted the first football world cup?",
    "Options": [
      "America ",
      "Argentina ",
      " Brazil",
      "Uruguay "
    ],
    "Ans": " Uruguay",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": "Which club won the 2017 UEFA Super cup? ",
    "Options": [
      "Real Madrid ",
      "Barcelona ",
      " Arsenal",
      "Bayern Munich "
    ],
    "Ans": "  Real Madrid",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": " Which football club does David Becham play for?",
    "Options": [
      "Manchester United ",
      "Liverpool ",
      "Real Madrid ",
      " Bayern Munich"
    ],
    "Ans": " Real Madrid ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 4",
    "Question": " Who won the 1998 Football world cup final?",
    "Options": [
      " France",
      " Brazil",
      " Portugal",
      "Wales "
    ],
    "Ans": " France",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 5",
    "Question": "Real Madrid plays football in which European country? ",
    "Options": [
      "Germany ",
      "Scotland ",
      " Spain",
      "Italy "
    ],
    "Ans": "  Spain",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 6",
    "Question": "Who won series-A in Italy in the 1999-2000 season? ",
    "Options": [
      " Arsenal",
      " AC Milan",
      "Lazio ",
      "Real Madrid "
    ],
    "Ans": " Lazio ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 7",
    "Question": "Who won the 1995 Woman’s world cup? ",
    "Options": [
      "Jamaica ",
      " Chaina",
      "U.S.A ",
      " Norway"
    ],
    "Ans": " Norway ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "8 ",
    "Question": "In what color strip do North Korea play in? ",
    "Options": [
      "Blue ",
      " White",
      " Red",
      " Yellow"
    ],
    "Ans": "White  ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  }
]



                                                                    Football / Hard



const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": " 1",
    "Question": "What year was modern football played? ",
    "Options": [
      "1941 ",
      " 1962",
      " 1703",
      " 1863"
    ],
    "Ans": " ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 2",
    "Question": "Which club won the most Champions League titles? ",
    "Options": [
      "Real Madrid ",
      " Arsenal",
      " Barchelona",
      "Bayern Munich "
    ],
    "Ans": " Real Madrid",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": " Liverpool was founded in which year?",
    "Options": [
      " 1899",
      " 1886",
      " 1900",
      "1905 "
    ],
    "Ans": "1886 ",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 4",
    "Question": " When was the first European Championship held?",
    "Options": [
      "1960 ",
      " 1975",
      "1945 ",
      "1990 "
    ],
    "Ans": "1960 ",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 5",
    "Question": " Whose player scored the fasted hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    "Options": [
      "Lionel Messy ",
      "Sadio Mane ",
      "Neymar ",
      " Ronaldinho"
    ],
    "Ans": " Sadio Mane",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 6",
    "Question": "In which year Ronaldo retired before changing his decision? ",
    "Options": [
      "2016 ",
      " 2014",
      " 2003",
      " 2008"
    ],
    "Ans": "2016 ",
    "eventCtg": "Football ",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "7 ",
    "Question": "Which is the largest football ground? ",
    "Options": [
      "Manchester united ",
      "Rungrado Stadium ",
      " Bayern Munich",
      "Arsenal Stadium "
    ],
    "Ans": " Rungrado Stadium",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Hard"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "8",
    "Question": "Whose country won the first world cup championship? ",
    "Options": [
      "Uruguay ",
      " Argentina",
      " Brazil",
      "Germany "
    ],
    "Ans": " Uruguay",
    "eventCtg": " Football",
    "quizCtg": " Hard"
  }
]



                                                                 Cricket / Easy

const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": "1 ",
    "Question": " The distance between the popping crease and the bowling crease is?",
    "Options": [
      " 4 feet",
      "5 feet ",
      "6 feet ",
      " 8 feet"
    ],
    "Ans": "4 feet ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 2",
    "Question": "  What was the official name of the first World Cup?",
    "Options": [
      "Prudential World Cup ",
      "Miani World Cup ",
      " World Cup",
      " Premier World Cup"
    ],
    "Ans": "Prudential World Cup ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 3",
    "Question": " Who won the maximum sixes award for the IPL 2008 season?",
    "Options": [
      " Sanath Jayasuriya",
      " Sachin Tendulkar",
      "Rohit Sharma ",
      "Virat Kohli "
    ],
    "Ans": "Sanath Jayasuriya ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": "The 1975 World Cup, the first of its kind was played at?",
    "Options": [
      "Lord’s London ",
      " Mirpur",
      "Kokata ",
      "Australia "
    ],
    "Ans": " Lord’s London",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 5",
    "Question": "Who won the first world cup, 1975 ",
    "Options": [
      "India ",
      "England ",
      " West Indies",
      " Australia"
    ],
    "Ans": "West Indies ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 6",
    "Question": " ",
    "Options": [
      " ",
      " ",
      " ",
      " "
    ],
    "Ans": " ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "7 ",
    "Question": " Who was the player of the IPL 2017 season?",
    "Options": [
      " Ben Stokes",
      " Sachin Tendulkar",
      "Rabindra Jadeja ",
      " Dinesh Kartik"
    ],
    "Ans": " Ben Stokes",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 8",
    "Question": " What is New Zealand cricket Brendon McCullum nickname?",
    "Options": [
      "Mac ",
      "Maccy ",
      "Bazz ",
      "Kate "
    ],
    "Ans": "Bazz ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  }
]


                                                        Cricke / Normal

const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": " 1",
    "Question": " What is the Australia’s highest score against India?",
    "Options": [
      "674 ",
      " 568",
      "690 ",
      "730 "
    ],
    "Ans": " 674",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": "How many times Chennai Super Kings won the IPL? ",
    "Options": [
      "3 ",
      "4 ",
      " 5",
      "6 "
    ],
    "Ans": " 4",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": "What players nickname is SOS (Son of Swamply) ? ",
    "Options": [
      "Shane Warne ",
      " Ricky Ponting",
      "Shaun Marsh ",
      "Gilchrist "
    ],
    "Ans": " Shaun Marsh",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": "Who is the no one All-rounder in cricket? ",
    "Options": [
      " Shakib al hasan",
      " Mustafizur Rahman",
      "Mashrafee Mortaza ",
      " Mushfiquer Rahim"
    ],
    "Ans": " Shakib al hasan",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "5 ",
    "Question": " The Ashes-who bowled the first ball of the 2019 series?",
    "Options": [
      "James Anderson ",
      " Mitchel Marsh",
      "Mohammad Shami ",
      "Mohammad Aamir "
    ],
    "Ans": "James Anderson ",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "6 ",
    "Question": "Who does the best batting average in a test career belong to? ",
    "Options": [
      "Don Bradman ",
      " Ricky Ponting",
      " Sachin Tendulkar",
      " Imran Khan"
    ],
    "Ans": " Don Bradman",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "7 ",
    "Question": "Australia’s first captain? ",
    "Options": [
      "Dave Gregory ",
      " Adam Gilchrist",
      " Mike Atharton",
      " Ricky Ponting"
    ],
    "Ans": " Dave Gregory",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 8",
    "Question": " Who captained India to victory in the world cup in 1983?",
    "Options": [
      "Kapil Dev ",
      " Ms Dhoni",
      " Saurav Ganguly",
      " Sachin Tendulkar"
    ],
    "Ans": "Kapil Dev ",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Normal"
  }
]



                                                                   Cricket / Hard

const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": " 1",
    "Question": "Which national team is nicknamed The Proteas? ",
    "Options": [
      "New Zealand ",
      "West Indies ",
      " England",
      "South Africa "
    ],
    "Ans": " ",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": " Which country has played the maximum number of one day matches?",
    "Options": [
      "Pakistan ",
      " England",
      " Australia",
      " India"
    ],
    "Ans": "Australia ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": "Name the first captain of the west indies team? ",
    "Options": [
      "Karl Hopper ",
      " Karl Nunes",
      " Juel Garner",
      " Chirs Gayle"
    ],
    "Ans": "Karl Nunes ",
    "eventCtg": " ",
    "quizCtg": " "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": " Named the player who was called Harmy?",
    "Options": [
      " steve Harmision",
      " Karlos Jackob",
      " Ricky Ponting",
      " Brain Lara"
    ],
    "Ans": " ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": " Hard"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 5",
    "Question": " The Asia cup was held at?",
    "Options": [
      "Sharjah,1984 ",
      " Mumbai, 1984",
      "Dhaka, 1984 ",
      " Colombo, 1984"
    ],
    "Ans": "Sharjah , 1984 ",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": " Hard"
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 6",
    "Question": "Name the only cricket to score five centuries in five successive innings? ",
    "Options": [
      " Karlos Jackob",
      " Brian Lara",
      " Everton Weekes",
      "Sachin Tendulkar "
    ],
    "Ans": " Everton Weekes",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": " Hard"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "7 ",
    "Question": "Who has been the first hat-thick recorded in Test? ",
    "Options": [
      "Fred Spofforth ",
      " Kieron Pollard",
      " Makahya Ntini",
      "Shaun Pollock "
    ],
    "Ans": "Fred Spofforth ",
    "eventCtg": "Cricket ",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": " 8",
    "Question": "Sunny Days is a well-known autograph of a world-famous player name, who is he? ",
    "Options": [
      " Mushfiquer Rahim",
      "Sunil Gavaskar ",
      "Ricky Ponting ",
      " Cameron"
    ],
    "Ans": "Sunil Gavaskar ",
    "eventCtg": " Cricket",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  }
]




                                                                    Basketball / Easy


const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": "1 ",
    "Question": "What is the highest governing body of basketball? ",
    "Options": [
      " EuroLeagur",
      "NBA ",
      "FIBA ",
      " DNBA"
    ],
    "Ans": "FIBA ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": " When was basketball made?",
    "Options": [
      "1737 ",
      "1974 ",
      "1784 ",
      "1891 "
    ],
    "Ans": "1891",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": "Who made basketball? ",
    "Options": [
      " James Naismith",
      " William Morgan",
      " Jim Thorpe",
      "Nill Kantone "
    ],
    "Ans": "James Naismith",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": "A free throw is worth? ",
    "Options": [
      " 1 point",
      " 2 points",
      "3 points ",
      " 4 points"
    ],
    "Ans": " 1 point",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "5 ",
    "Question": "A rebound is? ",
    "Options": [
      "A type of mode ",
      " A techanique",
      "A statistics ",
      " An array"
    ],
    "Ans": " A statistics",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Easy "
  }
]


                                                                          Basketball / Normal                                          

const quizeDtatStructure = [
  {
    "eventID": "1 ",
    "Question": "The regulation goal in basket ball is — feet high?  ",
    "Options": [
      "5 ",
      "  10",
      "  15",
      " 20 "
    ],
    "Ans": " 10 ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Normal "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": "Traveling results in …..?  ",
    "Options": [
      " an infraction",
      " a point ",
      " a redo ",
      " a dribble "
    ],
    "Ans": "  an infraction",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3 ",
    "Question": " The two lines at each end of the basketball court are known as ……? ",
    "Options": [
      "Base lines ",
      " Endzones ",
      " Parallels ",
      " Others "
    ],
    "Ans": "  Base lines",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4",
    "Question": "Sidney Wicks attended?  ",
    "Options": [
      " MIT",
      " UCLA ",
      " Harvard University ",
      " Others "
    ],
    "Ans": "  UCLA",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Normal"
  },
  {
    "eventID": "5",
    "Question": "  Which currently active NBA player has the most points?",
    "Options": [
      "LeBron James ",
      " Stephen Curry ",
      "  Dirk Nowitzki",
      "  Ferret Nowkit"
    ],
    "Ans": " LeBron James ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Normal"
  }
]


                                                                      Basketball / Hard


const quizeDtatStructure =[
  {
    "eventID": "1 ",
    "Question": " Who was the tallest NBA player on the 1992 Dream Team? ",
    "Options": [
      " Patrick Ewing ",
      "  David Robinson",
      "  Larry Bird ",
      " Others"
    ],
    "Ans": " David Robinson ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "2 ",
    "Question": "  In theory, an NBA game is —----- long?",
    "Options": [
      "  48 minutes",
      "60 minutes  ",
      "  2 hours ",
      "3 hours "
    ],
    "Ans": " 48 minutes ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "3",
    "Question": " How long can a defensive player stand in the paint without guarding anyone?  ",
    "Options": [
      " 3 seconds ",
      " 5 seconds ",
      "  7 seconds ",
      " 10 seconds"
    ],
    "Ans": " 3 seconds ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "4 ",
    "Question": " The first coach of the year award was presented to? ",
    "Options": [
      "Harry Gallatin  ",
      " Steve Kerr ",
      " Rick Carlisle  ",
      " Bill Russell"
    ],
    "Ans": " Harry Gallatin ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  },
  {
    "eventID": "5 ",
    "Question": " Physical contact between two players is what kind of foul? ",
    "Options": [
      "  Personal foul",
      "Flagrand foul  ",
      " Technical foul  ",
      " Others "
    ],
    "Ans": "Personal foul  ",
    "eventCtg": " Basketball",
    "quizCtg": "Hard "
  }
]




  
